{"data":[{"question":"This couple, together with their new friends, ___there already.","a":"have been","b":"has been","c":"will be","d":"had been","answer":"2","explain":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin-bottom:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;line-height:\nnormal;mso-layout-grid-align:none;text-autospace:none\"><span style=\"font-size:\n10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">-<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">Phrases such as <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:\nPMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">together with<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;\nmso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;\nfont-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">, <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;\nfont-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">as well as<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:\nPMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">, and <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;\nmso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;\nfont-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">along with<span style=\"font-size:\n10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">: <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">The phrase introduced by <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;\nmso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;\nfont-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">as well as<span style=\"font-size:\n10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\"> or <span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;mso-fareast-font-family:\nPMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">along with<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;;\nmso-fareast-font-family:PMingLiU\">'<span style=\"font-size:10.0pt;\nfont-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\"> will modify the earlier word, but it does not compound the subjects--The subject is 'this couple' which is singular and requires singular verb (has been)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"The rest of the plot ___ very wonderful.","a":"are","b":"were","c":"seem","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"- With words that indicate portions - percent, fraction, part, majority, some, all, none, remainder, and so forth - look at the noun in your of phrase (object of the preposition) to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb\u00a0\n- The plot is singular--The rest of the plot is\/seems\u00a0very wonderful.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"I know that all the students ___ getting on well with Teddy.","a":"were","b":"was","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"- Subject (all the students) is plural\u00a0\n- Simple present tense (same tense with \"know\")\n(Verb tense consistency on the sentence level:\n+Keep tenses consistent within sentences.\u00a0\n+Do not change tenses when there is no time change for the action.\n-Verb tense consistency on the paragraph level:\n+Generally, establish a primary tense and keep tenses consistent from sentence to sentence.\u00a0\n+Do not shift tenses between sentences unless there is a time change that must be shown).\n\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"When and where this event took place ___ still a mystery.","a":"were","b":"are","c":"has","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"Usually, but not always, two or more than two wh-clauses would have a singular verb: Each of the clauses introduced by wh-clauses can be considered as a single unit of thought, and therefore the verb should be the singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Not only the equipment but also the workers ___ not there.","a":"were","b":"have","c":"has","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin-bottom:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;line-height:\nnormal;mso-layout-grid-align:none;text-autospace:none\"><span style=\"font-size:\n10.0pt;font-family:&quot;Tahoma&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;\">- To be + adverb\/preposition: used to say where something or someone is\n-Not only. . .but also, and neither. . .nor: The subject closest to the verb determines whether the verb is singular or plural\u00a0\n-- the subject is 'the workers' which is plural and requires plural verb (were)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Some reporters _________ Henry's address in the suburb.","a":"know","b":"knows","c":"has known","d":"are knowing","answer":"1","explain":"- Subject (some reporters) is plural, it takes plural verb\n-Some verbs are normally used in the simple form because they refer to states, rather than actions or processes:\u00a0\n+Verbs refer to mental state (know, forget, mean, imagine...) are not usually used in continuous form.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Everyone except the boss _________ excited.","a":"have","b":"has","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"3","explain":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal; mso-layout-grid-align: none; text-autospace: none;\"><span style=\"font-size: 10.0pt; font-family: 'Tahoma','sans-serif';\">- To be + adjective: used to describe someone or something\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Nothing _________ on that topic.","a":"has been","b":"has said","c":"has been said","d":"is","answer":"3","explain":"- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs\n- Present perfect tense + Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Every tool ___ tried then.","a":"have been","b":"has been","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"- Subject (every tool) is singular \n- Present perfect: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Each man and each woman in the factory ___ to help in the work.","a":"are asked","b":"is asked","c":"had asked","d":"ask","answer":"2","explain":"- Use each: when you are thinking about the people or things in a group separately, one by one\n+ 'Each' is followed by a singular verb\n- Passive voice: be + participle (is asked)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"}]}